For boarding students at Bodwell, there is much more to consider
Bodwellの学生寮で生活するにあたり
throughout the day than an average high school student
普通の高校生より、1日のスケジュール的に多くの事を期待されています。
Students here are expected to responsibilities in all area their life
ボドウェルの学生は、新しい環境、学校、スタッフ、友人との生活に
while adapting to a new environment, new school, and new people.
適応していく中で、色々な面で、責任ある生活を求められます。
It can be very overwhelming.
最初は、難しいことと感じるかもしれません。
For this reason, it is necessary to establish a routine that students can follow,
その為、ボドウェルでは、1日のスケジュールを提示し、学生たちは、
to help them structure their day and develop the proper time management skills needed
そのスケジュールの中で、自分のルーティーンを確立させ、時間管理能力を高める事で、
to be successful in all areas of a boarding student's life
有意義な、寮生活を過ごす事が可能になります。
A student's day begins with the wake-up call at 7 a.m.
学生達の１日は午前7時の起床から始まります。
By 8:00, all the boarding areas are closed and students
午前８時までに寮施設が閉鎖され、
are not allowed to re-enter until the end of the academic day.
学生達は１日の学校終了時間まで寮に戻ることができません。
We want students to develop the habit of bringing everything they need from their home to class
私たちは、学生達が自室から授業に必要なものすべてを持ち込む習慣を身につけて欲しいと願っています。
Breakfast is available from 7:25 to 8:15 every morning
朝食は毎朝7時25分〜8時15分です。
Breakfast is an important meal and we encourage students to eat by extending meal time past boarding closure.
朝食は重要な食事です。私たちは、朝食の時間を少し長くとることによって、学生たちが確実に朝食をとれる様、工夫をしています。
At 3:30 p.m. The school day ends and clubs begin. These run from 3:30 to 4:30
午後3時30分、授業時間が終わり、各クラブ活動が始まります。クラブ活動時間は3時30分〜4時30分です。
This is a great opportunity for students to work on
この時間はクラブ・課外活動が
an extracurricular activity for once,  sometimes twice a week
週１～２のペースで行われます。
From 5:30 dinner is available for all boarding students.
午後５時半、寮生達の夕食がはじまります。
Our cafeteria stays open during supper for 45 minutes
校内カフェテリアの夕食時間は４５分間です。
Study-hall begins at 6:00 with small group tutoring for those requiring extra help
その後、6時から学習に遅れがある生徒達の為の、少人数でのサポート授業が行われます。
At 7, Junior study all begins and at 8:15 we have senior study hall, where all senior students attend.
午後７時、低学年の学生のスタディーホールが始まり、８時１５分に高学年のスタディーホールが始まります
The library also remains open through the evening.
図書館も寮生のために、夜も開放しています。
Every Wednesday each individual Hall meets for announcements
毎週水曜日、寮のホールごとのミーティングがあります。
and to discuss issues and further develop life skills and community building.
寮内のお知らせ、問題の話し合いなどを行います。
Every hall meeting is run a little differently.
ミーティングの内容、方法は各ホールで違いがあります。
It allows each hall to develop an individual sense of community within the boarding program.
このミーティングでは、自分達が所属するホールの一員としての意識を高める事も目的です。
After study hall snack is available in students of thirty minutes free time
スタディーホール後、３０分間のフリータイムがあり、そこでは夜のスナックが用意されています。
to begin heading back to their halls for curfew.
その後、門限までに各々のホールに戻る必要があります。
By 10:15 students are up in their boarding halls and begin their bedtime routines.
門限は、１０時１５分。その時間までにすべての生徒が寮に戻り、就寝前の準備をします。
We give students an hour for their bedtime routine.
消灯時間前の１時間は各生徒が
This is a time for students to wash up,
就寝準備・翌日の準備時間にあてたり
build a sense of community in their halls as well as relax and reflect before bed.
友人と話をしたり、リラックスする為に時間を過ごします。
We have a student that goes around to do the curfew check to-
寮で行える学生の仕事として、各部屋を回り門限チェックをする学生もいます。
We give them some volunteer hours for that.
門限チェックを担当する生徒には、学生のボランティア参加時間が加算されます。
And then later on the evening we'll go around again just to make sure that everybody is where they're supposed to be.
その後、寮スタッフが各部屋を回り、生徒が自身の部屋にいるかの最終確認も行います。
At 11:00 all students are in their rooms followed by a lights out at 11:30
すべての学生は１１時までに自分の部屋に戻る必要があり、１１時３０分が消灯時間です。
Although the weekend schedule varies,
週末や冬・春休みは、消灯時間やスケジュールが一部変わりますが、
here in boarding we like to keep a structured weekday routine,
平日のスケジュールは、学生達が、
to allow students to focus on academics and further develop their life skills.
規則正しい生活を行い、学習に集中できる様、スケジュールが設定されています。